<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Developer Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Developer Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/description/</guid>
      <description>About me Smart Kind Some info </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/programming/</guid>
      <description>Programming Skills My programming skills are already quite versatile and I&amp;rsquo;m always ready to learn more.
Most used languages are:
Python TypeScript Rust C I&amp;rsquo;m the most familiar with following techs:
MySQL/MariaDB ElasticSearch Express.js Selenium (with Python) AWS Currently learning/using:
WebAssembly (My thesis researches using WASM to process audio 🎵) Rust (This language feels like the future&amp;rsquo;s C) Hugo CMS1 (This web site was made with Hugo 😉) CMS = Content Management System&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/projects/</guid>
      <description>My Projects Below are a few of my projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve made during my studies or on my free time. Most of these are pure passion projects which I have made because I have wanted to learn some tool, technology or I have wanted test implementing some algorithm.
Battleship Game (with hunting algorithm) A game of battleship agains AI using hunting algorithm. The game is made in Python is modular in a sense that players can be used to do another things like playing completely another game by creating an interface for the player!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/soft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spoilaro.github.io/portfolio-site/soft/</guid>
      <description>Soft Skills I&amp;rsquo;m generally quite outwards person and I like to converse with people. I would say that my strong suit is learning new things and helping others to learn the things I&amp;rsquo;ve learned along the way.
What I would like to improve is my time management. In 2023, I want to incorporate the usage of calendar (yes, calendar 📅) to my workflow to manage time and resources.
Overall, I have enjoyed working with people in daily basis but I also appreciate the quietness that comes along the profession called software developer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
